There is an enormous wall in front of me, blocking my way.
I can only wonder what's on the other side.
What does it look like?
If I have others with me, maybe one day I'll see it.
I'll see the view from the summit.
You ready, Hinata?
Yeah!
The body of the Cinematheic細胞 heart gets revealed
I'mkam Goji
I'm
Knowing
Against
The
Cheering
Thank you.
Of course. I wouldn't miss this for the world. You were great.
I mean...
All right, fellas. Let's get moving.
Really great.
It'd be even greater if you'd expand your vocabulary.
Um, Yui?
Yeah. All right.
I got this for you.
No, wait. I mean, it's not for you.
No, wait. That came out totally wrong.
This is for you, and for the team, too, of course, to share in...
Oh, how thoughtful.
Thanks, Yui. You're so considerate.
Huh?
Oh, it's no problem, really.
I'll keep it on the bench with us.
Thanks again.
Cheer us on!
You know we will!
At least you were able to pull it off without drooling all over him.
Man, this place is packed ass to ears.
Well, that's the finals for you.
Look at all these guys.
You better not chicken out on us, Tanaka.
What? You want to say that to me again, little man?
Huh?
Listen, dude. This is very important.
On the court, all eyes will be on us.
And I don't just mean the guys.
Picking up what I'm putting down.
Am I, uh, picking up...
No kidding. It's so hot when they bring a sweat on the court.
So sexy.
Aw, yeah!
Everything you do is so cool, Mishinoya.
Tanaka, you're so handsome.
Mishinoya! Tanaka!
Um...
Do your best, okay?
Thank you for the insider intel.
Let's get out there and give it our all, bro-chacho!
Sounds like a plan.
Most of you guys were made for each other.
Hey! You guys are embarrassing the whole team, you know?
Those two.
Well, it's good to see they're the same as always.
Will you two shut up?
Very true.
Let's go already!
Don't forget to pee-pee, Hinata!
I did already!
Sure you did.
Hey, Sho!
Izumi! Koji!
Hey, Sho-yo. It's been a minute.
Uh...
Uh, they're friends of mine.
From my middle school volleyball team.
Or, technically, they were warm bodies so I'd have enough players.
Yeah, um, I play basketball.
I'm on the soccer team.
Sounds like you don't have the right skills to get those nice kills, huh?
Hmm?
Don't look now, but that a-hole dude from our game is here.
Yeah, funny story. He's my teammate now.
He can be a little intense sometimes, but he has his reasons.
But he's that king, jerkwad, right?
You sure you're gonna be okay?
Heh heh.
Sure, I got this.
Huh?
Yo!
Let's go, Hinata!
Huh?
Gotta run! Thanks for coming!
Knock him dead, Sho!
Okay!
Wow, we've really been out of touch with him lately, haven't we?
He's come such a long way.
Are those guys your friends?
You played them, remember?
Why would I?
Do you remember every single bug that you've squashed?
See, Kageyama, this is exactly why no one likes you!
You little...
Stop that!
Don't you think you moron should conserve your energy?
You're gonna need it to win the finals, you know.
Well, I guess we might lose in straight sets anyway.
Get along, sir.
You two are the worst.
All right, let's go!
Okay, let's put our stuff upstairs.
Hey, what'd you stop for?
That Karasito team sure hasn't gotten a lot of buzz.
Well, I guess they did lose in the second round last time.
I hope them making it this far hasn't been some kind of fluke.
That old coot again, what the heck is his problem?
Wait, you know him?
I don't.
Just seen him at all our games.
He's been coming around for a pretty long time.
I guess he's a big fan of high school volleyball or maybe just Karasino itself.
Cheers the plays he likes and cheers the ones he doesn't.
You can't miss him.
He's always been easy to spot.
You've really never noticed that guy before?
Maybe.
I think I might have seen him at a tournament way back when we were just first years.
You will not call us wingless crows again.
Guys, let's do this!
Yeah!
I can't believe we made it this far.
Yeah.
Let's take this thing.
You know it.
Okay!
Let's get this day started off on the right foot, people.
We've got the Karasino Shopping District, Alumni Cheer Squad, and some incoming students.
We are going to be a zillion times louder than Shiratorizawa.
Listen up!
A good team is only as strong as its cheer squad is loud!
Make sure to give it everything you've got!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight!
Wow, the vice principal is really taking things seriously, don't you think?
One, two, three!
Was he always like this?
It goes go, go, Karasu no!
Push it, push it, Karasu no!
Go, go, Karasu no!
What was that, you pansies?
We practiced this yesterday!
Sir, give them a break.
We didn't have very much time to run through the cheer after school yesterday, okay?
It's not looking so great.
Look, we have to keep it together, man!
Let's do it for the boys!
I mean, see how confident they are?
I'd better hit the bathroom one more time before I go out there!
We're at center court!
They're everywhere!
There's chicks all over the place!
It's too much!
Get up off the floor!
Are you five?
Five is optimistic.
Hey, calm down!
Nobody freaked out!
So this is the team, huh?
I said I'm not a creeper!
Oh?
This ghoul was lurking around here and ran away as soon as I locked eyes with him!
He's gotta be a spy for Shiro Torizawa!
Wait, what?
Hold on, my name's Akiteru!
I'm Kei Tsukishima's big brother!
That guy has a brother?!
Shh!
He told me not to come!
You're gonna blow my cover!
Quiet!
Yeah, I don't see the resemblance.
These guys are totally different.
Huh?
Shiro Torizawa!
Come on, let's go!
Today we'll be playing!
Karasu Noha!
Good luck!
Come on, let's go!
That's something else.
Yeah, well, they are a powerhouse school, after all.
Speaking of, Shiro Torizawa's not here yet.
Yeah, they're late.
And we still have to sit through their stupid cheer?
Ugh!
Guess champions get to take their time.
Yeah, well, champions or not, that's just tacky.
They're here.
Let's go!
Heil!
Bye!
Okay, guys, let's have a quick meeting.
Now, I know you boys are tired from playing two games in one day,
but listen up.
The big match is tomorrow, guys.
There's no room for error, so I'll be frank with you.
If Aoba Josai is the most complete team in the prefecture,
then Shira Torizawa is the most incomplete.
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, you don't need me to tell you.
Your managers were thoughtful enough to compile all the information
they could get about Shira Torizawa into these pamphlets,
so make sure you read them cover to cover.
Ms. Kiyoko made this just for me?
No, I made them for everyone.
We wanted to help you guys out any way we possibly could.
Isn't that right, Yachi?
Uh, yeah.
I'm glad I could be useful to you guys.
You're the best, Yachi!
They worked really hard on this thing.
You need to memorize every square inch of it.
Sir!
Hey, uh, coach, what did you mean by incomplete?
If you think of the attacks and movements we usually use on the court as multiplication,
then there's his addition, adding strong individuals together.
Our game focuses on timing, positioning, and speed.
And we're good at it.
Now, they've got pretty decent timing, too.
But their receives are sloppy.
And wherever they stick their wings, Spiker, that's where they plan to score.
Their preference is to give Ushiwaka high sets.
The reason is obvious.
His height and jumping ability is an advantage.
My bad!
Keep your guard up.
They're gonna come out swinging.
You have never experienced a team this strong.
So be ready.
How'd he manage to hit it all the way up here in the nosebleeds?
That guy has an arm.
They're certain to rely on their best weapon tomorrow.
That's the kind of team they are.
Ushiwaka is a force to be reckoned with.
But don't underestimate the rest of them, either.
They all bring something to the table.
My arm would break if I tried to hit that.
They make it look so easy, don't they?
Ushiwaka.
He's so awesome.
Now I'm super pumped up.
Yeah.
Let's go!
Inside!
Charge!
Huh?
I got it!
Is your name Benkei?
He was Ushiwaka's right-hand man in that old story.
Hey, Rayon!
What's up?
Rayon?
That little Karasuno score just called you Benkei.
Where the heck did he get that name from?
I don't know.
I don't really get it.
That shorty is half of Karasuno's quick attack duo.
What?
For real?
Let's do this!
Aw, look at that little tweet down there.
He's so small.
What if he's subbing for someone?
He's kind of cute.
I have a thing for rooting for the underdog.
Not a kill!
All right, you two.
Do what you did yesterday.
One last thing, and I can say this with great confidence.
You are every bit as good at this game as they are.
Just remember, take control from the start.
What just happened?
He shot it straight down?
He's a quick one!
Did the center even touch the ball?
You know, guys, I was bummed that Seizhou didn't come this year.
But they seem pretty fun, too.
You got that right.
Whatever they throw at us, we will be sure to force them to surrender!
You shouldn't talk smack if you can't back it up.
Nah, nah, play nice.
Don't you worry about it, Goshki.
Your words are as cool as your bangs.
Oh, yeah? You think so?
You know, I don't think it's a good idea to baby him the way you do.
Easy, man.
You're too tight, Taichi.
I have faith in this fella.
This guy's the chosen one.
He's gonna be the ace after us third years are gone, you know?
I won't let you down!
Yeah, we know.
Just do your best, Mr. Future Ace.
Stop. You're gonna make his ego even worse.
Okay, we're first to receive.
Roger that, buddy.
Kick some ass for us.
You have to pull your own weight, too.
Don't just lean on Ushiwaka.
Sorry to put too much pressure on him, Ben-K.
Ushiwaka!
In this next game, I promise I'm going to prove myself worthy of the title of Future Ace of Shira Torizawa.
Oh, yeah? Do your best, then.
I think he's actually being sincere, even if he sounds like a deadpan jerk.
Their starting lineup is just what we thought.
Did everybody study up?
Yeah!
Everyone needs to keep a level head out there.
If these guys take a point, get it back.
Ushiwaka is only human, and he's bound to slip up.
You know what to do, right?
Right!
Remember, you guys, this is the finals.
We've made it this far, so let's win and make our way to nationals!
We will now begin the final game of the National High School Volleyball Qualifying Tournament.
This game determines Miyagi's representative and the overall winner of all boys' teams.
Our challengers are Karasano High School and Shira Torizawa Academy.
Please give them a warm welcome.
This is it?
Wow, the show looks really tiny down there, doesn't he?
Jeez, are we sure they aren't playing against college kids?
Whoa, they've got cameras everywhere in here.
At this time, I'd like to introduce Karasano High School's starting lineup.
Number one, Daichi Sawamura.
Number three, Asahi Adumane.
Number five, Ruinosuke Adumane.
Asahi Adumane.
Number nine, Togeo Kageyama.
Number ten, Shouyo Hinata.
Eleven, Kei Tsukishima.
Suki, look who's here!
Keep it doing!
Number four, Libero.
Yu Nishinoya.
Oh yeah!
And their coach, Itetsu Takeda.
And now, please allow me to introduce the players of Shira Torizawa Academy's starting lineup.
Number one, Wakatoshi Ushijima.
Number four, Weyuan Ohira.
Number five, Sasaya Tendo.
Number eight, Stomu Goshiki.
Number ten, Kinjiru Shirabu.
Number twelve, Taichi Kawanishi.
Number fourteen, Libero Hayato Yamagata.
And their coach, Tanji Washijo.
Ladies and gentlemen, please give the athletes of both teams a round of applause.
Our game will begin momentarily.
Man, you can get the Jinjin in here with a knife.
Our guys look like they're ready and raring to go, though.
They've got their game faces on, especially Hinata.
Shira Torizawa's done all this a million times already.
But it's our guys' first time in center court.
First time in the finals, too.
So you know our guys will be nervous, but you can't blame them.
It's their first final, which means they've never played a five-set match before.
Five sets?
That's right.
Up until today, they've always played best two out of three.
But during the finals, it'll be best three out of five.
It's just like the professional matches on TV.
Wow.
They're gonna be exhausted.
Probably.
Stamina's a big concern.
Well, I think the best baby won't fix it!
This looks like a different start than usual.
Yeah, you're right.
They normally kick off a game with Hinata up front and center.
I guess they're trying to put the tall guys in front to deal with Ushiwaka.
I'm curious to see how they handle his spikes.
Bring it!
But I don't have time for a team that couldn't beat Alba Josai in the prelims.
You can talk all you want, but I'm not listening.
Serve it up, Captain!
I got it!
Ushiwaka!
Here it comes.
It's mine!
Nice kill!
Ushiwaka!
Good try!
Get the next one!
Oh, I see, Lefty.
Who needs help?
Ushiwaka!
Thank you.
ここに高く生きたいのだ
あとは君次第です
全部君次第
きっと甘い甘いと言われても
違うよ 違う 溶けなされたって
あとは君次第
迷うんじゃない
君次第
ご視聴ありがとうございました